say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother James yes
sir and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage Thou shalt have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquity of
the fathers upon the children unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy manservant nor thy maid servant nor
thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth Earth the sea
and all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee Thou shalt not kill
Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not steal Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor Thou
shalt not covet thy neighbor's house
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's wife
nor his man's servant nor his maid
servant nor his Ox nor his ass nor
anything that is thy neighbors I read
Exodus 20 veres 1-1 17 may the Lord add
a blessing to the reading of this word
in Jesus name we pray
amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time the questions
that we will not answer are the B
questions the long scripture questions
and the questions of debate we are not
here to debate we are just here to
spread the true Gospel of God so please
be direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other books or
Bibles will be acknowledge on this
program also keep in mind that this is a
live stream so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just ask that you keep your
questions to or two scripture maximum
but let me introduce to you the family
that's on the panel this evening brother
Julius good evening everybody brother
Dre good evening brother Jerome Grace
and peace brother James good evening
everyone sister Deborah good evening
brother Sean good evening and we have
the guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening uh yes there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's
Q&A um Jun
norford asks in Genesis 4: 5 through 7
the last sentence in verse seven what
desire is God talking about and who is
he referring to all right so in that
Genesis
45-7 brother Dre can you share some
light there yeah let's go to Genesis 4
and we gonna read verses 5 through S and
we'll deal with
that go ahead brother James and read it
but unto Cain and to his offering he had
not respect and Cain was very wroth and
his countenance fell and the Lord said
unto Cain why art thou wroth and why is
thy countenance Fallen if thou doest
well shalt thou not be accepted and if
thou doest not well sin lith at the door
and unto thee shall be his desire and
thou shalt rule over him so if we don't
do well sin lith at the door and When
sin is finished it will bring forth
death but let's go over to Romans the
6th chapter Romans
6 Romans 6 and we gonna read verse 12
and we're going to skip from there
Romans 6 and verse
12 okay go ahead let let not sin
therefore reign in your mortal body that
ye should obey it and the lust
thereof go ahead Nei neither yield ye
your members as instruments of
unrighteousness Unto sin but yield
yourselves unto God as those that are
alive from the dead and your members is
instruments of righteousness unto God so
what Cain did was was bring forth an
offering and he was wroth and then he
wind up killing his brother so that sin
took over
and it led to death and it was it was
the it it ruled over Cain but read verse
16 go ahead know ye not that whom you
yield yourselves servants to obey his
servants ye are to whom ye obey whether
of sin unto death or of obedience unto
righteousness that's right so whoever
you lend yourselves members servants to
obey whoever you yield yourselves
servants to
obey his servants you are to whom you
obey whether it be of sin orto death are
of obedience onto
righteousness so who was Cain led by
let's go to First John 3 and we just
gonna read verse 12 and that'll be it
First John 3 and verse
12ad John 3 and verse 12 says not not as
Cain who was as was of that Wicked one
and slew his brother and wherefore slew
he him because his own Works were evil
and his brothers righteous so Cain's
Works were evil because he was led by
that Wicked one and that and the desires
of that Wicked one ruled over Cain
because he was led by that
one that's all I got on that
all right there was some good light
there brother and that advice that the
lord gave Cain just applies to everybody
just do well yes sir all right thank you
for that brother hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
uh next one Mrs way asked in scripture
John 13
verse2 who is this Simon judah's Father
scripture makes it seeing we should know
who Judah father
is all right John 13 and2 who is this
talking about here brother
Jerome uh it is what it says but let's
go read
it St John 13:
ver2 and supper being ended the devil
having now put into the heart of Judas a
scariot Simon's son to betray him yeah
so we understand and know that it's not
Simon Peter we know that for sure okay
and there's plenty Simon mentioned
throughout the New Testament but this
place that we reading right here it
talks about Judas iscariot's father and
what his name was and it said Simon and
we can't we can't add anything else to
that so that's all I got and then and
then brother Jerome it don't say his
father it says Simon's
son yeah not his
father all right hope that anwers your
question there we continue to move on
moving on can you explain Proverbs 11
verse
15 brother Julius can you explain
Proverbs 11 verse1 15 yes sir let's go
to that brother James Proverbs 11
remember proverbs are wise
sayings Proverbs 11 and pay attention to
how the scripture is written go ahead at
15 he that is shy or stranger shall
smart for it and he that hateth sure
shers ship is
sure he that is shy for a stranger shall
smart for it shity is like a
guarantee okay and in other words what
it's saying if you cosign for a stranger
it's going to come back and bite
you if you cosign for a
stranger is going to come back and bite
you you're taking on somebody else's
debt that you don't debt that you don't
even know and if they can't pay you're
liable for that that's what it means he
that it says he that is shy for a
stranger shall smart for
it and he that hath Spirit ship is sure
why because you don't cosign and you
don't support uh cosign for strangers
you don't support cosigners for
strangers because it's a bad
deal you got another example of it in
Proverbs the 20th chapter Proverbs
20 here that word is again
Proverbs
20 and look at just burn look at the
half the top half of verse 16 Proverbs
20 and verse
16 take His Garment that is shy for a
stranger take His Garment that is shy
for a stranger it's like it's like a uh
insurance for for a stranger take His
Garment now you got something to hold
case you don't come
back yeah that's all I got I hope that
help
yeah you're right brother and sometime
even the ones a little closer to you you
got to be careful cosigning for them too
yeah all right hope that answers your
question as we move on moving on Solomon
TV true word unored asks does our pastor
make supplications and private atonement
prayers for the church on a normal basis
I got this
from the priesthood in Leviticus chapter
4 and chapter
16 okay so um we GNA ask the guest
caller to share some light on this
question well go read Leviticus chapter
4 where should I start start at verse
one okay Leviticus 4:1 says and the Lord
spake unto Moses saying Speak unto the
children of Israel saying if a soul
shall sin through ignorance against any
of The Commandments of the Lord
concerning things which not to be done
and shall do against any of them if a
pre if the priest that is Anointed do
sin according to the sin of the people
then let him bring for his sin which he
has send a young bulock without blemish
unto the Lord for a sin
offer and he shall bring and he shall
bring the bulock unto the door of the
Tabernacle of the congregation before
the Lord and shall lay his hand upon a
Bullock's head and kill the bulock
before the
Lord go ahead and the priest that is
Anointed shall take of the Bullock's
blood and bring it to the Tabernacle of
the congregation and the priest shall
dip his finger in the blood and sprinkle
of the blood seven times before the Lord
before the veil of the
sanctuary and the priest shall put some
of the blood upon the horns of the altar
of sweet
incense uhuh verse verse 20 and it'll
tell you what happened okay he when he
blood before the veil read verse 20
verse 20 says and he shall do with the
bulock as he did with the bulock for a
sin offering so shall he do with this
and the priest shall make an atonement
for them and it shall be forgiven
them now first thing is that's under
levitical priesthood where you took the
blood of an animal to make an atonement
for the people so the qu answer to the
question is
no the blood of Jesus
do that go to Hebrews the 10th
chapter yes
sir read verse one and then skip down
and read verse
[Music]
4-10
okay Hebrews 10
verse1 says for the law having a shadow
of good things to come and not the very
image of the things can never with those
sacrifices which they offered year by
year continually
make the comers there unto
perfect verse four beginning at verse
four says for it is
not now it's talking about the law this
is the law of animal
sacrifice now no matter how many people
went before that veil with the blood of
the Bullock and sprinkle it it could not
make them perfect perfect mean they
could not become God why is it that that
blood didn't help SK down to verse four
now and go ahead
for it is not possible that the blood of
bulls and of goats should take away sins
wherefore when he cometh into the world
he saith sacrifice and offering thou
wouldest not but a body H has thou
prepared me and burnt offerings and
sacrifices for sin thou Hast had no
pleasure then said I lo I come in the
volume of the book it is written of me
to do thy will oh God above when he said
sacrifice and offering and burnt
offerings and offering for sin thou
wouldest not neither has has pleasure
therein which are offered by the law
then said he lo I come to do thy will oh
God he taketh away the first that he may
establish the second by the which will
we are Sanctified through the offering
of the body body of Jesus Christ once
for
all so now that is the one it is the
blood of Jesus that do that skip down
and read verse
14 for by one offering he have perfected
for even them that are
Sanctified so now he is the one that
makes supplication for the people and
for the
church they no preacher do that
blood of animals couldn't do that only
the blood of
Jesus that's all I have to say all right
thank you for that we hope that answer
that question as we continue to move on
to our
next yes uh the next one is he also ask
in Leviticus 5
verse1 what does it mean
all right and that Leviticus 5 And1 what
does it mean brother
Julius let's read it brother James okay
I'm there go ahead brother and if a soul
sin and hear the voice of swearing and
is a witness whether he has seen or
known of it if he do not utter it then
he shall bear his iniquity soul is a
body if a it's identifying what sin uh
what a soul is and it also telling you
if you have sin or hear sin or be a part
of sin confess it acknowledge it confess
it repent and save yourself if you don't
hey you can very well pay for that sin
that's the best I can do with
that all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered that question
as we move on to our next one okay uh
moving
on uh
Solomon the next one is
from Solomon
says Solomon TV true word unavoided says
does our pastor make
supplications and prayer atonement
prayers for the
church excuse me the n question will be
from Andrew and Andrew says I'm not in
I'm not an Israelite by Blood so when
Jesus returns will I be taken to
Jerusalem with Israel or will I return
to the land where my forefathers came
from also will it be the same when the
fathers when the father comes down to
earth and Ezekiel
37:14 is
given all right so look like they got
quite a bit to that question there uh
guest caller can you take it from
there go to Ezekiel the 37th verse and
read the 14th verse let's see what it's
talking
about Ezekiel 37 and14 says and shall
put my spirit in you and ye shall live
and I shall place you in your own land
then shall ye know that I the Lord have
spoken it and performed it sayeth the
Lord where that's coming from is when
the Lord come he is going to teach the
people that's when he come that's not
the father's Kingdom that's Jesus okay
but as for as the other concerned if
you're not an Israelite then will you go
uh uh with the people some strangers are
going that's if you want to go and if
you uh don't want to go then you can go
back to the country of your Nativity but
we show you but if you but some will go
and let's go into Ezekiel the 47th
chapter read verses 13 and 14 and then
we're going to
skip okay Ezekiel 47: 13 and 14 says
thus sayeth the Lord God this shall be
the Border whereby ye shall inherit the
land according to the 12 tribes of
Israel josu shall have two portions and
ye shall inherit it one as well as
another concerning the which I lifted up
mine hand to give it unto your fathers
and this land shall fall unto you for
inheritance now skip down to verse 21
and read to verse 23 okay so shall ye
divide this land unto you according to
the tribes of Israel and it shall come
to pass that ye shall divide it by lot
for an inheritance unto you and to the
strangers that sourn among you which
shall begot children among you and they
shall be unto you as born in the country
among the children of Israel they shall
have inheritance with you among the
tribes of Israel and it shall come to
pass that in what tribe The Strangers to
join
there shall ye give him his inheritance
sayeth the
Lord so if this
stranger is a servant of the Lord and he
go with Israel just like it was when
Israel when Israel came out of Egypt he
say it was a mixed
multitude so whatever when the Lord
start passing out the land then the
stranger if he's a whatever tribe he's
among he have to have an inheritance to
so you're not an Israelite and you and
you keep the laws and statutes with
Israel and you want to go to the land of
Israel with the people you you
can't as for as the father's condition
uh uh father's uh uh kingdom is a little
bit different let's go into Revelation
the 21st chapter read verses 1 and
three 1 2 3 verses 1
to Revelation 21: 1-3 read okay and I
saw a new Heaven and a new Earth for the
first Heaven and the first Earth were
passed away and there was no more sea
and I John saw the holy city New
Jerusalem coming down from God out of
Heaven prepared as a bride adorned for
her husband and I heard a great voice
out of Heaven saying behold the
Tabernacle of God is with men and he
will dwell with them and they shall be
his people
and God himself shall be with them and
be their
God read just a little more and God
shall wipe away all tears from their
eyes and there shall be no more death
neither sorrow nor crying neither shall
there be any more pain for the former
things are passed
away now that New Jerusalem coming down
that's that's that's that's God going to
come with it that's the holy city New
Jerusalem that's going to come down and
God going to dwell Among Us it says man
but we won't be man at that time
everybody be God and who is going to be
saved skip down and read verse
24 verse 24 and the nations of them
which are saved shall walk in the light
of it and the kings of the earth do
bring their Glory and Honor into
it now everybody be Mortals then so you
will uh uh won't it won't be like uh
this tribe and that tribe everybody's
going to be mortal you come out of
somebody and you come out of a Nation
but everybody's going to be holy and
everybody's going to be God but for the
first part of it sure just like it was
in Egypt it was a mixed multitude if
you're not an Israelite and you dealing
with the god of Israel and you want to
go with the people of Israel then you
can like I said in Ezekiel you will get
an inheritance in the land that's all I
have to say right no respected persons
with
God all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
our next question 103 MJ asks what does
Romans 4 verse5
mean Romans 4 and5 brother Jerome what
does that
mean let's go go read
it you get it go ahead all right Romans
4:5 says now to him that worketh is the
reward not reckoned of Grace but of
debt okay oh I'm sorry verse verse five
I'm sorry that was verse four but to him
that worketh not but believeth on him
that justifieth the ungodly his faith is
counted
righteousness okay um one thing is clear
is we do have to keep um The
Commandments of God we have to do those
works that's something we have to do um
but in that fifth
verse um that's not the subject that
Paul is really addressing what he's
addressing in that verse is he's
addressing Grace and Faith so skip up
and read verse four for me okay
verse four now to him that worketh is
the reward not reckoned of Grace but of
debt yeah yeah so what he trying to tell
you is your your works is not what's
paying the debt you know and neither is
the law of animal sacrifices paying your
debt okay so let's go to um the third
chapter okay you know it's it's the Lord
Jesus Christ faith in him and faith in
his blood that's what's actually paying
the debt okay and so this is what Paul
trying to address in that fifth verse
read uh the third chapter and read verse
23- 26 okay Romans 3: 23- 26 says for
all have sinned and come short of the
glory of God being justified freely by
his grace through the Redemption that is
is in Christ Jesus whom God has set
forth to be a propitiation through faith
in his blood to declare his
righteousness for the remission of sins
that are passed through the forbearance
of God to declare I say at this time his
righteousness that he might be just and
the justifier of him which believeth in
Jesus so this righteousness mentioned in
this verse it's the same righteousness
he referring to in that fifth verse of
the fourth chapter is Faith In Jesus and
faith in his blood and what he did for
us to redeem us okay and to cover our
sins you know so that's what Paul trying
to say you know you you got to have
faith in order to get access to this
forgiveness of your sins all right faith
in him and faith in his blood that's not
saying you don't have to keep the
Commandments of God
okay so skip down to verse
okay do we then make void the law
through faith God forbid yay we
establish the law all right so we we we
still required to keep the law all Paul
trying to tell you is but if you ain't
got faith in Jesus and faith in his
blood you don't have access to this
Grace whereby you can receive the
forgiveness of sin you got to have them
both okay that's all I got on it let me
throw up being on it yes sir yes I just
I just want to point another side to it
when Adam sinned against God and God
called the death sentence on us there
was no way
out right but then Jesus came and died
for our sins and gave us the way out but
there was nothing we did did that caused
Jesus to die he came and did that as a
free will and therefore it was uh a
Grace is a free
gift so Adam took your eternal life away
from you and Jesus came and gave you
back access to eternal
life and he didn't do it because you
have worked he did it because he wanted
to save the save the creation but now
once you have your access to the true of
life then you got to do what God told
Adam in the beginning you got to obey
him that is your
wors just just like you're going and
getting hir on the job you didn't do
nothing to get hir but once you got high
you got to do something to keep it
yeah all right yeah hey brother Jerome
thank God for that Grace
okay thank you all right we hope that
ansed your question there sister de we
gonna keep moving with a Time
Check Yes uh moving on and the time is 8
o'l um 103 MJ also asks in Joshua 7
verse 6 is he breaking the second
commandment I don't think so brother
Julius can you share some light on at
Joshua 7 and6 and is he breaking the
second
commandment let's break this
down brother James Joshua the 7th
chapter and read verse 6 okay and Joshua
rent his clothes and fell to the Earth
upon his face before the Ark of the Lord
unto the even TI he and the Elders of
Israel and put dust upon their head
all right the question is why is Joshua
why did Joshua and the elders fall
down and
uh before the Ark of the Lord this
scripture has this scripture has nothing
to do with idol worship is he breaking
the second commandment no let's go find
out let's go to Exodus the 20th chapter
and read the second
commandment Exodus
and read verse four okay Thou shalt not
make unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth all
right so now let's go and look at this
Arc let's go to the 20 25th chapter of
Exodus okay and why was the Ark made
the Lord asked Israel to take up an
offering
willingly and so that let the book Speak
Exodus 25 and pick it up at verse eight
and we'll skip when you get it go ahead
James and let them make me a sanctuary
that I may dwell among them so the
purpose of their Ark let them make me a
sanctuary that I might dwell among them
verse
10 and they shall make an ark of
shamwood two cubits and a half shall be
the length thereof of and a cubit and a
half the bre thereof and a cubit and a
half the height thereof so this is the
ark but what was the purpose of that
give me verses 21 and 22 go ahead and
thou shalt Put The Mercy Seat of above
upon the ark and in the ark Thou shalt
put the testimony that I shall give thee
and there will I meet with thee and I
will commune with thee from Above The
Mercy Seat from between the two chairs
which are upon the Ark of the testimony
of all things which I give thee in
commandment unto the children of Israel
he said I'mma meet with you at the ark
so the same thing he had told Moses tell
Israel build the ark put the mercy SE
inside the ark that represented God
among Israel okay so now let's when we
go back to Joshua the 7th chapter and
read Israel saying because the Lord told
Israel in the sixth chapter not to take
of their cursed thing well ancient sin
and 36 men died Israel could stand
before their enemies and so that's why
Joshua and them ripped their clothes and
fell to the Earth they went to the ark
because the Lord told you I'm gonna meet
you there and I'm going communicate with
you there so they was it was a out
showing of repentance uh for sin they
were seeking the Lord for forgiveness
and for counsel
and so the Lord counsel them go find the
man that Sinn take
him so that uh he could pay the price
for the penalty of for the wages of sin
so that it had nothing to do with idol
worship it just had something to do with
seeking the Lord for counsel and
covering their dust and ring their
garments with an outward showing of
repentance and forgiveness and seeking
the Lord for
counsel yep and that that was the Arc of
the true and living God and not a false
god right and they were not worshiping
it according to the second commandment
they were seeking the Lord for counsel
because that's where the Lord said I'm
going meet with you and there will I
instruct
you all right thank you for that brother
hope that answer that question as we
keep on
moving yes all day production says in
order for the temple that the false
prophet
Prophet will occupy to be built will the
Dome of the Rock necessarily have to be
torn
down I don't think so but in order for
the temple that the false prophet will
occupy with the Dome of the Rock need to
be torn down guess
caller well we don't know
that because the old Temple don't that
that that that don't necessarily have to
be where the old Temple was built the
old Temple was built in the uh uh thresh
and flow of
AR and there are the people that and
there uh certain uh uh uh Publications
that say that where the temple is built
right now is where the Roman car
Garrison was and that and that was not
where uh
uh the uh uh old Temple was
built and uh so we don't know where the
temple is going to be built so we can't
answer the question because nobody's
come up with the exact location of the
first and the second
temple so have to say all right thank
you for that hope that answered that
question as we move on to our next one
next question Tracy Burgess says
can you explain the Sabbath
day sure we can it's a very good
question the Sabbath day also known as
the seventh day of the week also known
as Saturday let's go into uh Genesis the
chapter Genesis the 1 chapter there's a
few things behind the Sabbath day and
what it means so let's read a few
scriptures there brother James we G to
do some skipping Genesis 1 and one when
you get there go ahead in the beginning
God created the Heaven and the Earth get
down to verse five and God called the
light day and the Darkness he called
night and the evening and the morning
were the first day so in this Genesis
we're going to see how the Lord used the
Sabbath day and he compared it with
numbers didn't have anything to do with
this modern day Monday Tuesday and
Wednesday the Lord set it all up with
numbers skip down to verse eight and he
was building or having stuff created
rather and he gave it a number what did
he do in verse eight and God called the
firmament Heaven and the evening and the
morning were the second day so the
second day he did the Firmin it of
Heaven skip down to verse
13 and the evening and the morning were
the third day and he brought forth the
grass and all of that on the third day
Skip down to verse 19 and the evening
and the morning were the fourth day yeah
and the Lord made the one light to rule
over the day the Sun and he made the
moon to rule over the night skip down to
verse
23 and the evening and the morning were
the fifth day and God blessed him and
said be multiple and replenish the Earth
talking about the uh animals in the sea
and the fire of the air skip down to
verse 26 and let's see this is when man
comes in on the sixth day go ahead and
God said let us make man in our image
after our likeness and let them have
dominion over the fish of the sea and
over the fowl of the air and over the
cattle and over all the Earth and over
every creeping thing that creepeth upon
the Earth uhhuh so God created man in
his own image in the image of God
created he him male and female created
he them so then God created man in his
own image and let's see what day that
was on skip down to 31 and God saw
everything that he had made and behold
it was very good and the evening and the
morning were the sixth day so we have
went through one through six now comes
the Lord's Sabbath day and that Genesis
2 pick it up at at verse one for me go
ahead thus the heavens and the Earth
were finished and all the host of them
and on the seventh day God ended his
work which he had made and he rested on
the seventh day from all his work which
he had made on the seventh day God
rested from all his work go Ahad and God
blessed the seventh day and Sanctified
it because that in it he had rested from
all his work which God created and made
so the seventh day God rested when he
was going through the numbers 1 through
7 he rested on the seventh day and that
is what we call the Sabbath day for
today now turn over to Exodus 31 right
quick Exodus
31 okay Exodus
31 as the modern day numbers Sunday is
the first day of the week and then if
you count Monday and Tuesday and
Wednesday you end up on Saturday as
being number seven which is the Sabbath
day so pick it up at at verse 12 and go
ahead let's read a little bit more about
the Sabbath Exodus 31 and2 go ahead and
the Lord spake unto Moses saying Speak
thou also unto the children of Israel
saying verily my sabbaths ye shall keep
for it is a sign between me and you
throughout your Generations that ye may
know that I am the Lord that doeth
sanctify you so this sabbath day let you
know that you are the Lord's people go
ahead keep reading ye shall keep the
Sabbath therefore for it is Holy unto
you everyone that defileth it shall
surely be put to death for whosoever
doeth any work therein that Soul shall
be cut off from among his people go
ahead six days may work be done but in
the seventh is the Sabbath of rest holy
to the the Lord whosoever doeth any work
in the Sabbath day he shall surely be
put to death so this is what we read in
Genesis the Lord said the seventh day is
the Sabbath day of rest and it is a holy
day go ahead wherefore the children of
Israel shall keep the Sabbath to observe
the sabbath throughout their generations
for a Perpetual Covenant so the Sabbath
day doesn't change it's still the
seventh day go ahead brother
it is it is a sign between me and the
children of Israel forever for in six
days the Lord made Heaven and Earth and
on the seventh day he rested and was
refreshed once again we see the Lord
rested now let's see who wrote that the
seven day was the Sabbath of the Lord
Verse 18 and he gave unto Moses when he
had made an end of communion with him
upon Mount Si two tables of testimony
tables of stone written with the Finger
of God oh written with the Finger of God
that's why he say it's perpetual it's
not any ending to it now turn over to
Luke and let's see what Jesus did when
he came in the flesh to die for the sins
of the whole world let's see what he did
on this sabbath day Luke 4
and14 Luke 4 and14 says and Jesus
answered him saying it is written that
man shall not live by bread alone but by
every word of
God and the devil taking him up into a
high mountain showed unto him you I I
just read four Luke 4 and4 4 and4 okay
and Jesus and Jesus returned in the
power of the spirit into Galilee and
there went out a Fame of him throughout
through all the region round about it's
the same Jesus that rested back in
Genesis go ahead and he taught in their
synagogues being glorified of all uhhuh
and he came to Nazareth where he had
been brought up and as his custom was he
went into the synagogue on the Sabbath
day and stood up for it to read oh so
Jesus went into the synagogue on the
Sabbath day that same number 7eventh day
that we read about in Genesis now modern
day today too CU nothing change that's
why he say it's perpetual let's go to
Isaiah 58 and see how you should keep
this sabbath even today because the Lord
said this is a sign between him and his
people very important day to the Lord
written with his own finger Isaiah 58
and13 go ahead if thou turn away thy
foot from the Sabbath from doing thy
pleasure on my holy day and call the
Sabbath a delight Delight the holy of
the Lord honor able and shall honor him
not doing thine own ways nor finding
thine own pleasure nor speaking thine
own words the Lord is now getting into
how he want us to keep his Sabbath day
the same Sabbath day which we said is
number seven which is Saturday go ahead
14 then shalt thou Delight thyself in
the Lord and I will cause thee to ride
upon the high places of the earth and
feed thee with the heritage of Jacob thy
father for the mouth of the Lord has
spoken it and that is just a small
snippet of the Sabbath day and what it
is that the Lord said who created it and
who had it written and that's all I got
anybody
else all right we hope that answered
your question there and we go move on
sister Deborah I believe we're going
into some new territory now uh yes we
are we are now into tonight Q&A for
Wednesday January the 1st
2025 um sister Israel says I need help
understanding John
7 versus 24 through 28 and verse
47 all right let's go to John 7 and
let's open it up to the
panel because she say she needs some
help with that John 7:2
24-28 and verse 47 so let's pick it up
at that 24 James and then let's open it
up to the panel okay go ahead brother
judge not according to the appearance
but judge righteous
judgment then said some of them of
Jerusalem is not this he whom they seek
to kill but Lo he speaketh boldly and
they say nothing unto him do the do the
rulers know indeed that this is the very
Christ yes how be this is the Christ
they talking about here but he's saying
in verse 24 judge not according to the
appearance he tell us don't judge
according to the outward appearance but
judge righteous judgment because it's
the heart that really determines where
you coming from go ahead how be it we
know this man whence he is but when
Christ cometh no man knoweth whence he
is then cried Jesus in the temple as he
taught saying ye both know me and ye
know whence I am and I am not come of
myself but he that sent me is true whom
ye know
not I skip down to 47 and let's see what
the panel has for that then answered
them the Pharisees are ye also
deceived let's go to John the first
chapter chapter on that John 1 John
1 and and read verses 1 through3 okay
John 1 veres 1-3 says in the beginning
was the word and the Word was with God
and the Word was God the same was in the
beginning with God all things were made
by him and without him was not anything
made that was made skip down to verse 10
he was in the world and the world was
made by him and the world knew him not
so it's not a wonder that they didn't
know him because he was in the world he
was in the beginning with God and the
Word was God the world was made by him
and the world knew him not so they
didn't know him neither skip down to
verse
18 no man had seen God at any time but
the only begotten son which is in the
bosom of the father he hath declared him
so the god that no man has seen at any
time is the father no man has seen the
father at any time the son is the one
who declared him so this is what this is
talking
about I hope that help yes sir all
right thank you for that brother hope
that answer they question next question
uh next question is from Sandra Allen
that says I would like to know if
generational curses are a real
thing the Sunday churches teaches this
but I don't believe it because of
Ezekiel 18
verse2 am I
right all right speaking on behalf of
generational curses
correct yes all right so let's go to
Ezekiel
18 I'm there and uh pick it up at that
verse 20 and let's also open this up for
the panel because it looks like in this
verse 20 here that hey everybody got to
Bear their own iniquity go ahead
brother the soul that sent it all right
hold on one second call her well going
to say well she asked the question is
she right when you say uh Ezekiel uh
reverses that yes she's right yeah so
the S it shall die there ain't no
generation of curse only the curse we
have as a people when God called the
curse on Israel but the Lord
terminated the curse cursing the father
for the son or the son for the father so
the question was what was the question
again de uh yes the question
was um is this I would like to know if
generational curses are a real
thing what else did you
say uh the Sunday churches teach this
but I don't believe it because of
Ezekiel 18 verse vers 20 am I
right he's exactly right because of the
whole chapter of
Ezekiel so now if you don't sin you
don't get cut off the Lord say all sin
so the mind now you can start reading it
just a little bit just just the first
few verses start at Ezekiel 18
And1 Ezekiel 18 And1 says the word of
the Lord came unto me again saying what
mean ye that ye use this proverb
concerning the land of Israel saying the
fathers have eaten sour grapes and the
children's teeth are set on
edge as I live sayeth the Lord God ye
shall not have occasion anymore to use
this proverb in
Israel behold all All Souls are mine as
the soul of the the father so also the
soul of the son is mine the soul that
sinth it shall
die now that that tell the question
right there so the sister so whoever
answered the asked the question and said
that it said that there is no more
generational curse she is correct and
Ezekiel proved that the entire chapter
of the
18th of
Ezekiel m
[Music]
yeah yeah because in that question I
think she was saying too that the other
churches are teaching that there is a
generational curse but it is not
according to what we just
read yeah the other church is teaching
that you going to heaven too right
that's
right that Jesus was born the 25th day
of December right
y well everybody everybody's correct as
that there is about what they teach is
going to heaven
M yeah concern about what other churches
teach you concern yourself about what's
written in this book and it said the
soul that s it it shall die that's right
yeah weel 4 and 20 answers
it
yeah all right I hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next next
one Andrew asks what is an earn vessel
Leviticus 11 verse 33 is
given Leviticus 11 and 33 Why Don't We
Go There what is an earn
vessel and we're going to also open this
up to the panel Leviticus 11 let me get
there verse 33 you said yes yes all
right go ahead and read that brother and
every Earth and vessel whereinto any of
them fth whatsoever is in it shall be
unclean and ye shall break
it all
right bases cups plates anything that's
made from the ground right pots and pans
all that can be an earth and
vessel
yep okay hope that that aned your
question as we move on again yes KY
Kaz Lee asked in Exodus 12 verses 1 and
two is this saying that the month should
begin with March instead of
January Exodus 121
and2 and let's read it and Endeavor
repeat that question read Exodus 121
and2 James and the Lord spake unto Moses
and Aaron in the land of Egypt saying
this month shall be unto you the
beginning of months it shall be the
first month of the year to
you and the question the question again
in uh Exodus 12: 1 and two is this
saying that this month should begin with
March instead of January
well that month is the month
ab and whatever month that AB start that
is the beginning and that usually start
around the last of March or the 1st of
April yes
sir not January so the New Year have not
come in yet New Year won't come in and
if if somebody had a calendar you can
look at it and it will tell you right
now
when the uh New Year
start anybody have a
counter I think
it's March the 29th I think yeah I think
it's March 29th too search mode brothers
and let's see what we come up with here
that's that's when the new moon show up
right yep I think
so uh
it says the first month of the new moon
is Saturday March 29th y yep March 29th
that's
it okay so that's when the month that's
when the Lord's month's SC that is the
beginning of the month
AB
okay you can uh read about AB in the
very next chapter in the 13th chapter
and the fourth verse
it lets you know that that is the month
AB so we talking about the time of the
Passover around the
Passover
that's that's the beginning of the
Lord's M
yes yeah end of March or be or first
week in April when things are starting
to Bud and come to life not in the day
of the winter
all right we hope that anwers your
question as we move on to our next one
uh the next question Andrew asked can we
eat raw fish or meat not fully
cooked no when you eat raw fish and meat
that's not fully cooked when it's not
fully cooked it involves blood and the
Lord say you're not supposed to eat the
blood
there tanel what else
if you if you could figure out how to
get the blood out of it you
can't the Lord only when he telling you
about you can eat these animals he said
don't eat the blood so if you can figure
out how to get the blood out of without
cooking
then the Bible don't say you
can't just can't eat the
blood right and that is written in
Genesis 9 and4
Genesis 9
and4
okay Genesis 9 and4
says but flesh with the life thereof
which is the blood thereof shall ye not
eat yes
sir that's it don't eat the
blood y right CU I know cooking can help
to remov the blood out of the other
beasts that we are allowed to eat yes
sir y all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next yes
the next one is from Malik
Shakur and uh he says in Mark 9 vers 2
through
7 Jesus was standing with Peter James
and John John when Peter proceeded to
speak with Jesus so if no one has ever
heard God's voice at any time who was
speaking in Mark 9 verse
7 all right let's go to Mark 9ine and
verse 7 because that Still Remains true
no one has heard the father's voice at
any time or seen his shape but pick it
up at that Mark 9 and2 and let's open it
up to the pth mark 9 and2 says and after
six days Jesus taking with him Peter and
James and John and leadth them up into a
high mountain apart by themselves and he
was transfigured before
them and his reignment became shining
exceeding white as snow so as no Fuller
on Earth can wi them and there appeared
unto them Elias with Moses and they were
talking with Jesus and Peter answered
and said to Jesus Master it is good for
us to be here and let us make three
Tabernacles one for thee and one for
Moses and one for Elias for he was not
what to say for they were sore afraid
and there was a cloud that overshadowed
them and a voice came out of the cloud
saying this is my beloved Son hear
him okay first thing is we want to stand
as a fact go and read St
John 5 and 37 yes sir St John 5 and 37
says and the father himself which have
sent me hath borne witness of me ye have
neither heard his voice at any time nor
seen his
shape okay now that rul the father out
so let's show who did the speaking from
Heaven let's go to Genesis the 22nd
chapter yes
sir and we're going to start reading
that uh uh
uh you want to get direct to the point
versus Genesis 2 11 and 12 well 11 let
me do it the way I want to do it yes sir
Genesis 22
And1 okay Genesis 22 And1 says and it
came to pass after these things that God
did tempt Abraham and said unto him
Abraham and he said behold here I
am now see I want to let you know that
it's God's talking here keep reading and
he said take now thy son thy only son
Isaac whom thou lovest and get thee into
the land of Mariah and offer him
therefore burnt offering upon one of the
mountains which I will tell thee
of now he said it's God's talking right
let's see what Abraham get down to verse
n verse 9 and they came to the place
which God had told them of and Abraham
built an altar there and laid the wood
in order and bound Isaac his son and
laid him on the altar upon the
wood go ahead and Abraham stretched
forth his hand and took the knife to
slay his son and the angel of the Lord
called unto him out of heaven and said
Abraham Abraham and he said hear am
I oh oh so it was an angel that call
right that's right yeah now let's get
now let's get right on down to
uh verse uh uh
uh
15 and the angel of the Lord called unto
Abraham Out of Heaven the second
time uhhuh read 16 and said by myself
have I sworn sayeth the Lord for because
thou has done this thing and has not
withheld thy son thine only
son now so the angel of the Lord that's
doing it and the angel of the Lord talk
like they God sometime because they
would tell you uh uh and the Lord said
and the Lord said it because he ain't
speaking his own words he's speaking the
words of the Lord now when the Lord told
Israel I'm going to send an angel before
you obey he said oh he uh obey his voice
and do all that I
say so when that Shad came over Peter
them and said this is my beloved Son and
whom I am well
pleased that was an angel but he speaks
like he is
God you can go and read where an angel
in the bush spoke to Moses and that same
scripture tell you and the Lord
said Blas Blas
you get my point yeah that tell you what
the angel you ain't never heard the
voice that's what the Lord have the
angel I give you one other thing and
this will be it let's go into Joshua uh
uh judges the second chapter that's up
judges the 2
chapter
uhuh okay start reading at verse two
when you get
there judges 2 and 2 says and ye shall
make no league with the inhabitants of
this
land uhuh one verse
one judges 2 and one says and an angel
of the Lord came up from gilgal to bolum
and said I made you to go up out of
Egypt and have brought you into the land
which I swear unto your fathers and I
have said I will never break my Covenant
with you now
you know the angel talk like he made
Israel to go up out of the land he
didn't God made Israel to go up out of
the land and he said and I said I will
never break my Covenant with you the
angel ain't made no Covenant with nobody
who they made a covenant
with with God yeah go ahead and read and
ye shall make no league with the
inhabitants of this land ye shall throw
down their altars but ye have not obeyed
my voice why have ye done this he said
but you have not obeyed my voice why
have you done
this but the voice that the that the
people that the ones that told Israel
was an angel keep on reading wherefore I
also said I will not drive them out from
before you but they shall be as thorns
in your sides and their God shall be a
snare unto
you go ahead and it came to pass pass
when the angel of the Lord spake these
words unto all the children of Israel
that the people lifted up their voice
and
wept so now that voice they heard in the
cloud while it was out on the mount was
the voice of an
Angel that's all I have to
say one more
passage go ahead let's go to Exodus
read uh 20- 22
Exodus
23 ver 20- 22 yes
sir behold I send an angel before thee
to keep thee in the way and to bring
thee into the place which I have
prepared beware of him and obey his
voice provoke him not for he will not
pardon your transgressions for my name
is in him so the angel coming in his own
name
he cometh in the name of the
Lord go ahead but if Thou shalt indeed
obey his voice and do all that I speak
then I will be an enemy unto thine
enemies and an adversary unto thine
adversaries for mine Angel shall go
before thee and bring thee in unto the
amorites and the Hittites and the
perizzites and the Canaanites and the
hivites and the jebusites and I will cut
them off okay that's
good yes sir y it covers all the times
there was an angel speaking even at
Jesus baptism and it said this is my
beloved Son and whom I am well pleased
that was an angel a guest caller say yes
sir also in what he just
read where he said obey his voice and do
all that
that is right okay
yep yep all right hope that Shar some
light on that question that you asked as
we move on to our next one uh moving
on uh Zion
says please explain Mark 10 verse 31 who
are the first and who are the last is
this verse talking about the rich and
poor also in Mark 8 verse
34 who
does what does take up what does take up
his cross being so again the first one
is to explain Mark 10 verse 31 who are
the first and who are the last and they
imply it might be talking about the rich
and the poor and the second question is
Mark
8:34 what does take up his cross
mean right let's go to Mark
10 okay I'm there and pick it up at that
verse
31 and uh let's open it up to the panel
Mark
10 and 31
but many that are first shall be last
and the last
first all right open up to the
panel it have nothing to do with Rich or
poor it has to do people that claim to
be God to be uh claim that they serving
God and they look like they first but
they will not what the Lord said I think
it's in Matthew the 7th chapter where he
says uh everybody that say to me go Lord
Lord shall not enter into the kingdom
those that do my
will yeah that's in Mark 7 and verse 21
if you want to get straight to it yeah
okay they say a lot of you stood before
me saying Lord I've done many heal the
sick go go and read it okay yeah Mark
Mark 7 and verse 21 says not everyone
that sayith unto to me Lord Lord shall
enter into the kingdom of heaven but he
that doeth the will of My Father which
is in heaven many will say to me in that
day Lord Lord have we not prophesied in
thy name and in thy name have cast out
devils and in thy name done many
wondrous works and then I will profess
unto them I never knew you depart from
me ye that work iniquity
that's Matthews actually that you just
read right yes Matthew that was Matthew
7 and verse 21-
23 so these are talking about religious
people people that's in church all the
time and standing before God praying but
the problem is they ain't keeping his
commandments so he said I never knew
you but you got people in in the streets
that when they hear the word of God then
they start obey just like when Jesus
came when when the uh when John the
Baptist came the Pharisees didn't
believe him you know but the publicans
in the in the regular Street people
believe John the
Baptist some last that means somebody
that you don't expect uh uh uh uh to be
saved you don't hear them holling and
jumping up and down and screaming but
still they keeping the
Commandments and they just regular
people they are the land
but then people that's in the churches
screaming and holling talking how holy
they are but ain't keeping the
Commandments they are the first so that
mean that uh these people here
that's doing what God say they going to
get into the kingdom but all these
people are screwing and holling and
professing to serve God and not keeping
his commandment they are not going to
get into the
kingdom got who's serving God and who's
not yeah
yeah all
right and other one is Mark go ahead
Deborah yes it is uh Mark 8 vers 34 what
does take up his cross
mean all right Mark let's go to Mark 8
and 34 I'm there and um let's pick it up
because they want to know what does that
pick up that cross mean you have to
follow after Christ so um pick it up at
that verse 33 and read down go ahead
okay but when he had turned about and
looked on his disciples he rebuked Peter
saying get thee behind me Satan for thou
savest not the things that be of God but
the things that be of men so we have to
savor and follow the things that be of
God read that
34 and when he had called the people
unto to him with his disciples also he
said unto them whosoever will come after
me let him deny himself and take up his
cross and follow
me here we go to Luke the 9th
chapter Luke n yep it's GNA say the same
thing that's gonna say
it I mean the the same thing this time
pick it up brother James at 22 and let's
look at what Jesus
said Luke 9:22 and
23 saying the son of man must suffer
many things and be rejected of the
elders and chief priests and scribes and
be slain and be raised the third day go
ahead and he said to them all if any man
will come after me let him deny himself
and take up his cross daily and follow
me
so he told you in the 22nd verse you got
the son of man got to suffer many things
and be uh and be uh slain and crucified
and and uh uh ridiculed abused so if you
going to follow Christ you got to deny
yourself and you going to follow him and
be willing to suffer like he
suffered
y be rejected family your friends and
everything yeah y That's right God first
brother all right hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one with the time check uh yes the time
is
8:46 and both love asked in Mark 10
verse 40 does that mean God has it
prepared for two people to sit on the
right and left hand of Jes Jesus or does
that mean something
else Mark 10 and verse
40 yes all right let's uh let's read
that okay Mark 10 let's pick it up let's
pick now what was the question again
Deborah uh the question was does that
mean God has it prepared for for two
people to sit on the right hand and left
hand of Jesus or does that mean
something
else let's pick it up at verse 35
someone was requesting to sit on his
right hand and on his left and let's
read down into that uh 30 you say
38 uh
40 40 okay pick it up at 35 let's read
down we'll get a little more of the
story here go ahead
and James and John the sons of Zebedee
come unto him saying Master we would
that thou should us do us do for us
whatsoever we shall desire and he said
unto them what would ye that I should do
for you what they they said for they
said unto him Grant unto us that we may
sit one on thy right hand and the other
on thy left hand in thy Glory what did
he say but Jesus said unto them ye know
not what ye ask can ye drink of the cup
that I drink of drink of and be baptized
with the baptism that I am baptized with
and they said unto him we can and Jesus
said unto them ye shall indeed drink of
the cup that I drink of and with the
baptism that I am baptized with a with
all shall ye be baptized but to sit on
my right hand and on my left hand is not
mine to give but it shall be given to
them for whom it is prepared and those
that endure to the end open to the
pattern well the whole thing is what did
he tell Peter to
them in Matthew the 19th Chapter when
Peter didn't ask they ask Peter asked
what should we get they told man to
forsake
all uh you going uh Matthews 19 it said
you going to sit on 12 thr verse 28 then
answer Peter and said behold we have
forsaken
all uh Matthew 19 and verse
207 I'm there Matthew 19 and 27 says
then answered Peter and said unto him
behold we have forsaken all and followed
thee what shall we have
therefore verse 28 says and Jesus said
unto them verily I say unto you that ye
which have followed me in the
Regeneration when the son of man shall
sit in the Throne of his glory ye shall
sit upon 12 Thrones judging the 12
tribes of Israel
now you in the king you sitting on 12
Thrones it said nothing by the right
hand or to the
left okay now you go into Revelation the
20th
chapter okay of the 19th Revelation the
19th Chapter and start
reading at verse
three okay Revelation 19 and verse
three hold on a second
okay uh
Bru the 19 is the
20 20th chapter I'm sorry okay and uh
verse four start reading at four okay
Revelation 20 in verse 4 says and I saw
Thrones and they set upon them and
judgment was given unto them and I saw
the souls of them that were beheaded for
the witness of Jesus and for the word of
God and which had not worshiped the
Beast neither his image neither had
received his Mark upon their foreheads
or in their hands and they lived in
reigned with Christ a thousand
years now he said he saw Thrones
he didn't say where they was
located said it his right hand or to the
left Jesus didn't say he could he said
only the father know
that that's the only answer we can give
you the one that he gave the
person all I have to say all right thank
you for that sister Deborah time check
as we move to our next question yes the
time is
8:52 uh me too
for you Jones ask in Exodus
23:20 is this Angel Jesus some people
think Jesus is an angel
messenger he is not he is not an Ang
yeah Jesus Is God
correct that is correct so let's go to
that Exodus Dre um you just read had
that read earlier Exodus 20 23 rather
and verse 20 so why don't you read that
again brother and Dre if you got
something to add in and want to know is
this uh Jesus here go ahead brother
Exodus 23 and verse 20 says behold I
sent an angel before thee to keep thee
in the way and to bring thee into the
place which I have
prepared beware of him and obey his
voice provoke him not for he will not
pardon your transgressions for my name
is in him but if Thou shalt indeed obey
obey his voice and do all that I speak
then I will be an enemy unto thine
enemies and an adversary unto thine
adversaries for that's good he
sent
okay go ahead guess
caller Jesus is not in an angel oh Jesus
hated Angels okay now let's the second
chapter what was that again Hebrews
chapter 2
okay and uh let's start to read that uh
uh let's
see the two is it War
where they talking about ministering
Spirits Hebrews
chapter start at verse five okay Hebrews
1 and verse 5 says For unto which of the
angel said he at any time Thou Art my
son this day have I begotten thee and
again I will be to him a father and he
shall be to me a
son go ahead and again when he bringeth
in the first begotten into the world he
saith and let all the angels of God
worship
him now he said that right but keep
reading and of the angels He saith who
maketh his Angel spirits and his
ministers a flame of
fire uh but unto the son he saith thy
Throne oh God is forever and ever a
scepter of righteousness is the scepter
of thy
kingdom go thou has loved righteousness
and hated iniquity therefore God even
thy God hath anointed thee with the oil
of gladness above thy
fellows that's talking about Jesus and
what did God call him God God call him
skip down and read verse 13 and we got
one more place after that read but but
to which of the angel said he at any
time sit on my right hand until I make
thine enemies thy foot
stol unto which of the Angel none of
them he said that to none and when Jesus
came in fact we go to two more places
when Jesus came and died for the sin of
the people let me show you what it says
let's go into Hebrews the 10th
chapter and we're going to start read
and uh uh uh verse 10 at the offering of
the body of Jesus Hebrews 10 and start
reading at verse 10 okay Hebrews 10:10
says by the which will we are Sanctified
through the offering of the body of
Christ once for
all and every priest standed daily
ministering and offering often times the
same sacrifices which can never take
away
sins go ahead but this man after he had
offered one sacrifice for sins forever
set down on the right hand of God yes
sir from henceforth expecting till his
enemies be made his foot stol we're
talking Jesus there right
y so why is he expecting to do it
because the Lord said he was going to
sit at his right hand now let's go back
to 110th chapter Psalm and read one
verse verse one y Lord
say 110th chapter verse one says the
Lord said unto my Lord sit thou at my
right hand until I make thine enemies
thy foot
stol now it's talking about Jesus the on
who get out there and die for the sins
of the people then you're raised
intervene God again then you come and
sit down at my right hand until I make
thine enemy thy foot
stol he said to he didn't say that to
any of the Angels neither then he said
to the angels thou my son this day have
I begotten thee which he said in the
psalm the 2 chapter and all and uh and
in Romans the first chapter tell you
when he became his son so
now you got a religion that teaches that
Jesus uh uh and Michael is an is the
same one no Jesus Is Not An Angel Jesus
created the Angels first chapter of St
John said he created the in the
beginning with the word the word was
with God and the Word was God and he was
beginning in the beginning with God and
all things was created by Him yes sir
and didn't create is not created through
the angel was
created Jesus don't have no beginning
and no
end that is correct so we hope that
answered your question and sister
Deborah we are down to our last
question all right uh the last question
is from Jennifer Love and she says I
would like to know if my spouse a
nonbeliever visit his mother's grave and
I wait in the car across the street from
the
cemetery when he returns to the car am I
unclean for one day or seven days
yes call
them one day one day long as she don't
get out and go into the graveyard if you
walk on the
graveyard and uh you steal one day but
if you touch a bone or a dead body out
there then you unclean for seven days it
just one day yep yep long as you stay
outside the graveyard stay outside the
cemetery that's it y all right sister
Deborah time check
the time is n o'clock wow time certainly
flies when you haven't F yeah indeed so
we' like to thank everybody from all
around the world who joined us this
evening and to be a part of our Q&A
and where bro and we say that if anybody
submitted a question we didn't have
opportunity to get to it please don't
resubmit it sister Deborah take it put
it in rotation and we will deal with
that question next week so thank you all
for tuning in and until we come together
again be blessed be safe stay prayed up
and may the Lord have mercy on us all
brother James close us out Our Father
which art in heaven Hallowed be thy name
thy kingdom come thy will be done in
earth as it is in heaven give us this
day our daily bread and for for give us
our debts as we forgive our debors and
lead us not into temptation but Deliver
Us from Evil for thine is the kingdom
and the power and the glory forever in
Jesus name we